A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Papers of the Council on Legal Education for Professional Responsibilities, Inc. (CLEPR) FA706
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Appendix B: CLEPR Grantees, 1975-1977
  1976 American Bar Association (3 grants) Antioch College Association of American Law Schools Case Western Reserve University Chicago - Kent College of Law Duke University Harvard University Institute of Judicial Administration University of Maryland University of Michigan (2 grants) University of New Mexico Northwestern University University of Oregon University of San Diego (2 grants) Seven Springs Farm Center University of Southern California Southwestern University Temple University University of Tennessee Texas Southern University Washburn University (2 grants)
  1977 Association of American Law Schools Antioch College Association of the Bar of the City of New York Fund, Inc. Hofstra University University of New Mexico New York University (2 grants) University of the Pacific University of Pennsylvania Rutgers University Yale University Association of American Law Schools Capital University University of Chicago Vanderbilt University
- Appendix C: CLEPR Officers and Directors, 1968-1978
  Appendix C: CLEPR Officers and Directors, 1968-1978
  CLEPR OFFICERS William Pincus, President Elizabeth R. Fisher, Secretary Victor J. Rubino, Treasurer Peter deL. Swords, Program Officer Maximilian W. Kempner, Secretary
  EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE MEMBERS Ferren, John M. Kelley, Florence, M. Kempner, Maximilian W. Marden, Orison S. McKay, Robert B. Pincus, William Sacks, Howard R. Seymour, Whitney North
  MEMBERS OF THE BOARD OF DIRECTORS Avery, William H. Cavers, David F. Ferren, John M. Gossett, William T. Hastie, William H. McKay, Robert B. Kelley, Florence M. Kempner, Maximilian W. King, Otis H. Levi, Edward H. Levin, A. Leo Marden, Orison S. Nabrit, James M. Nelson, Dorothy W. Pincus, William Robb, John D. Rubin, Alvin B. Sacks, Howard R. Schaefer, Walter V. Segal, Bernard G. Seymour, Whitney North Sneed, Joseph T. Thurman, Samuel D. Toll, Maynard J. Tondel, Lyman M.